This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Mankini Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cover path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy has broken out of Impel Down, the world's greatest prison,
and is currently headed to Navy Headquarters to rescue his brother, Ace.
Meanwhile, after being scattered across the globe,
the rest of the Straw Hats are locked in the midst of their own adventures.
The Friends' Whereabouts!
The chick of a giant bird and a pink showdown!
I getcha!
So it's gonna be even harder to break into Navy HQ than Impel Down!
They're anticipating Whitebeard's assault at any moment,
so they're prepared for all-out war.
And there's no doubt that they've manned the place with the most formidable
and infamous figures known to the world today.
None of us here want to get ourselves caught up in a full-blown war,
but I'm afraid that might be inevitable now.
A short time before any of this, positioned deep in the Grand Line,
we find Peachy Island, home of the Kamabaka Kingdom.
Damn it. I run and I run, but they never give up.
What's wrong, pumpkin? Aren't you one of us?
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Get over here! Get over here!
Crap! Quit chasing me!
Quiet!
This is messed up. They're freaking strong as hell.
They may be wearing dresses, but there's nothing sissy about these punks.
Oh, Nami and Robin, how I long to see your beauty once more!
Is that so?
There have been some candy boys in the past who have had trouble accepting themselves after washing ashore on the banks of our paradise.
No matter. We simply need to extend an elegant helping hand to the lost soul.
I suppose I should ask if he's strong.
He won't win any bodybuilding contests, but his kicks aren't a total mess.
Well, it's been ages since we've done so, but I think the traditional method of the Kamabaka kingdom would be best employed here.
Oh!
Don't you have anything better to do?
Go away!
Quit chasing me!
Why won't you leave me alone?
You'll see!
Why the hell I will?!
Where am I? I wasn't even looking.
Am I safe in here?
What the hell is wrong with you psychos?!
Ow! I've been waiting for you.
Hey, hold on. Who is this bastard?
You do not disrespect her like that. Her name is Lady Caroline.
You the queen here or something?
Me? The queen? Oh, please!
To be exact, I'm the queen substitute... Caroline!
You're just a stand-in?
Kamabaka kingdom is ruled by one alone. The legendary Queen Ivanka!
Call. It'd be presumptuous to call myself queen just because she's away.
I couldn't give two turds if you're the actual queen or not. You've clearly got their ears so get it straight!
I'm done here! This is hell! Now get me off of this rock!
Very well, I hear you. However, if you're so desperate to leave, first you must fight the strongest of our kingdom and win. Deal?
You're damn right it's a deal! Anything to escape this nightmare!
Ooh!
Okay! Let's get you changed into one of our traditional Kamabaka combat outfits before the match!
What? A costume? Seriously?
You're combat outfit, huh?
And I fell for it too!
Are you the queen?
Shut up, I do not!
I've had just about as much as I can take of this crap! Just fight me! I'll finish you off with a single blow!
Once I do, I can forget all about this idiotic island!
Ah! Gorgeous!
Really? You're the strongest one on the island?
Well, how do you think I became the substitute queen of Kamabaka kingdom?
My prowess in the Kamabaka style! I am the new Kamakenpo Grandmaster!
Substitute!
Would you stop doing that?
Come on! Let's just get this over with!
Gladly! I'll show you my moves!
Yeah, I don't plan on giving you the chance to get that far!
I hate to burst your bubble!
But you're going down with one kick!
And con-casse!
Now let the dust settle!
Huh? Where is he?
Right behind you, candy boy!
What the hell?
Why can't I land a single attack?
In his eyes!
Why does he keep looking down?
And what's up with those weird ducking moves?
Don't tell me he's looking at-
Ooh!
Nice upskirt, honey!
Ah!
Oh!
Fine!
What the hell?
Why can't I land a single attack?
In his eyes!
Why does he keep looking down?
And what's up with those weird ducking moves?
Oh, don't tell me he's looking at-
Ooh!
Nice upskirt, honey!
Hey, don't look, you perv!
Not that I care!
I mean, I'm a dude!
Why would I be embarrassed if you see my stupid underwear?
Cause I'm not!
I'm not!
Sounds like your maiden-like modesty is coming out.
That's the stupidest crap I've ever heard!
You're not getting under my skin!
What the hell do I care if you see my underwear?
Are you sure about that?
We're certainly not kicking quite as high.
Seems like proof that you really are embarrassed.
See?
Hey, don't measure my deadly kicks!
I'm only trying to show you that you have doubt in your heart.
Shut up!
You don't know what you're talking about!
Oh, don't I?
Whoa!
No, no, no!
Stop that!
As I thought, you're wearing your masculinity as a shield hiding your true feelings.
What?
There's no greater freedom than being yourself.
So, are you done with your kicking?
I take it that you're inviting me to attack you now?
New Kama Kenpo technique!
Awakening enemy!
Why?
It's just stupid underwear!
Right?
So why am I paralyzed with embarrassment?
Whoa!
Stop!
What?
Did I really just scream like a girl?
What's happening?
Why do I...
Why do I feel this way?
I'm so confused right now.
Am I...
I am...
I feel like I'm losing myself.
I'm letting go, and I'm...
becoming somebody else.
scream like a girl? What's happening? Why do I, why do I feel this way? I'm so confused
right now. Am I? I am. I feel like I'm losing myself. I'm letting go. And I'm becoming somebody
else. Dear Nami and Robin, how are you? I hope this finds you well. I do so look forward
to seeing the two of you again. I'm certain that when the time comes, we'll be better
friends than ever before.
Deep in the south blue lies Birdie Kingdom, where a race of giant birds reigns supreme.
Oh man, I really want off this stinking island. This place is seriously the worst. Birds treating
me like I'm their toy. And humans constantly trying to eat me in a hot pot.
If that's not bad enough, and it really is, the birds and humans won't stop fighting
each other. There's gotta be a way out of here.
calm down. I gathered up a nice dinner for you.
How are your legs feeling today? Did they get any better overnight? Here, let me take a
look. Quit moving around now. Hey, they're all healed up. Alright, better eat these to get
your strength back. You're sure lucky I was around. Just imagine, what if I've been out searching
for herbs or something?
This should fix an upset stomach right up.
What in the heck was that noise? Are the humans after me again? Please, please, help me.
You're sure lucky I was around. Just imagine, what if I've been out searching for herbs or
something?
When Iprüordal came to eat these to get them a hotpot?
Are the humans until they've been out searching for magic?
Until you can eat them a hot pot, don't give them a hot pot inside.
This should fix an upset stomach right up!
What the heck was that noise? Are the humans after me again?
Please, please, don't let them throw me in a hot pot. They're gonna eat me!
Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot! Hot pot!
That's a big cheeper.
I guess she must have fallen out of the nest.
She's way too young to communicate with me, although I can tell she's hurt.
That much is obvious.
Wow, that's really bad.
Not that I'm all that surprised. Just look how far she fell.
Hey, try not to move.
Come on, stop. You're only going to make it worse.
Hey, calm down and do what I say.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Oh, jeez, you sure do eat a lot.
You're going to wear me out if I have to keep collecting this fruit for you all day.
But she needs all the food she can get so she can grow up strong and be able to fly someday.
And then she can return to the nest.
Oh, yeah.
You've got to do me a favor when you learn to fly.
You can get me off this crazy island and take me to the Saba Odi Archipelago.
Loopy!
Here I come!
Awesome, huh?
I mean, it's almost like I planned it when I helped you out.
You've got to promise me, okay?
And don't forget about it.
Hey, knock it off.
That tickles you little monster.
Stop!
Oh, come on.
You do?
Do I really look that much like a damn fruit toy?
So warm.
It's great to see you guys again.
Not that I actually missed your ugly jerk faces.
Oh, hang on.
I wonder where she went.
Oh, wow.
Her legs are all healed up by now.
She must have gone out for a walk.
Whoa, what?
This is really bad.
I better find her fast.
Judging by these prints, she can't be far.
I starving, you guys.
We know.
We all starving.
That why we tried to find escaped raccoon, you dummy.
Why you think we here?
That was reindeer, you the dummy.
Shut up.
Who cares what it is?
We're going to catch and make some hot pot.
Now you talking.
We salivate.
Oh, no.
Not good.
Not good at all.
Hey, I found you.
I'm so glad you're okay.
I don't think it here, guys.
Shh.
So we check out another part of jungle, right?
Yeah, you're right.
Good.
They didn't see us.
So you went wandering and got lost, huh?
I guess it's safe to say you're better now.
But you've got to be quiet, okay?
Those guys will find us if we make too much noise.
No!
Shut up!
Oh, I did it!
Huh?
Right there.
Icy reindeer.
Icy bird, too.
Double hot pot for dinner tonight.
Chicken hot pot and reindeer hot pot.
Hide.
Oh!
Arf!
You're kidding me!
They've got us cornered!
Oh!
Nowhere left to go.
Give up, dinner!
Big bird's coming to save the sheep.
We shoot them away!
Awesome! Are you guys really coming to help us?
Your baby got hurt, but don't worry.
I've been taking care of her for you.
But you don't need to take me or anything, you big bastard!
I totally knew you were gonna do that!
Guard point!
And they're right back to fighting again.
Of course.
I guess she must be the mother.
Take care!
And don't forget the promise you made!
As soon as you get big enough and know how to fly,
you gotta take me to see my friends at the Saba Odi Archipelago!
I'm counting on you!
But how long is that gonna take?
How long am I stuck here for?
I'm officially sick to death in this stupid place!
What is wrong with the humans and the birds on this island?
Can't they just try to get along?
Bloopy!
Everybody!
Please get me out of here!
Robin is captured in a place known as Tequila Wolf.
A young girl named Sorin, who she befriended, seeks to help her,
but she can't do it alone.
Meanwhile, Usopp trains to become a hero of the forest,
but his appetite is proving to be a distraction.
On the next, One Piece!
The Friends' Whereabouts!
Revolutionaries and the Gorging Forest's Trap!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!